type Quiz = {
  question: string;
  choices: string[];
  answer: string;
};

export const quizData1: Quiz[] = [
  {
    question: "Civil",
    choices: ["自然の", "敵対的な", "市民の", "古代の"],
    answer: "市民の",
  },
  {
    question: "Visible",
    choices: ["隠れる", "感じる", "見える", "聞こえる"],
    answer: "見える",
  },
  {
    question: "Alternative",
    choices: ["伝統的な", "二次的な", "主要な", "代替の"],
    answer: "代替の",
  },
  {
    question: "Intense",
    choices: ["平凡な", "速い", "穏やかな", "激しい"],
    answer: "激しい",
  },
  {
    question: "Reverse",
    choices: ["一致する", "前進する", "逆の", "同じ"],
    answer: "逆の",
  },
  {
    question: "Economic",
    choices: ["身体的な", "文化的な", "精神的な", "経済的な"],
    answer: "経済的な",
  },
  {
    question: "Scary",
    choices: ["冷たい", "暖かい", "楽しい", "怖い"],
    answer: "怖い",
  },
  {
    question: "Immediate",
    choices: ["間接的な", "即時の", "長期的な", "遅延した"],
    answer: "即時の",
  },
  {
    question: "Minute",
    choices: ["緊急の", "一般的な", "微小な", "巨大な"],
    answer: "微小な",
  },
  {
    question: "Due",
    choices: ["適切な", "支払われるべき", "余分な", "無関係の"],
    answer: "支払われるべき",
  },
  {
    question: "Social",
    choices: ["秘密の", "社会的な", "個人的な", "自然の"],
    answer: "社会的な",
  },
  {
    question: "Financial",
    choices: ["情緒的な", "教育的な", "健康的な", "財政的な"],
    answer: "財政的な",
  },
  {
    question: "Wealthy",
    choices: ["幸せな", "裕福な", "中間の", "貧しい"],
    answer: "裕福な",
  },
  {
    question: "Common",
    choices: ["特別な", "固有の", "珍しい", "一般的な"],
    answer: "一般的な",
  },
  {
    question: "Inferior",
    choices: ["同等の", "劣った", "優れた", "競争的な"],
    answer: "劣った",
  },
  {
    question: "Entire",
    choices: ["全体の", "断片的な", "部分の", "局所的な"],
    answer: "全体の",
  },
  {
    question: "Permanent",
    choices: ["不安定な", "変わることのない", "一時的な", "永久の"],
    answer: "永久の",
  },
  {
    question: "Minor",
    choices: ["二次的な", "大きい", "小さい", "主要な"],
    answer: "小さい",
  },
  {
    question: "Major",
    choices: ["一般的な", "主要な", "無関係な", "二次的な"],
    answer: "主要な",
  },
  {
    question: "Obscure",
    choices: ["人気のある", "不明瞭な", "明確な", "一般的な"],
    answer: "不明瞭な",
  },

  {
    question: "Threat",
    choices: ["保証", "友情", "脅威", "機会"],
    answer: "脅威",
  },
  {
    question: "Virtue",
    choices: ["無関心", "怒り", "美徳", "欠点"],
    answer: "美徳",
  },
  {
    question: "Tension",
    choices: ["幸福", "緊張", "リラックス", "人間"],
    answer: "緊張",
  },
  {
    question: "Gratitude",
    choices: ["恐怖", "嫌悪", "無関心", "感謝"],
    answer: "感謝",
  },
  {
    question: "Violence",
    choices: ["協力", "暴力", "平和", "喜び"],
    answer: "暴力",
  },
];
